amember.com 2019-07-24

# Privacy Policy | aMember

### Introduction

CGI-Central respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We have, therefore, established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit CGI-Central’s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. 

**This website uses Google AdWords**

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the [CLIENT NAME] website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.  

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can  
[opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or  
[permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).

CGI-Central strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, CGI-Central intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained. 

### Information We Collect

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and/or a set of numbers, that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any web page within CGI-Central, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and/or IP address. The domain name and/or IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of CGI-Central, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. See also “Disclosure to Third Parties” below. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. 

CGI-Central may offer access to services that require registration. In that event, your registration and/or contact information may be used to send notification to you of CGI-Central products and/or services by e-mail. We maintain a strict “No-Spam” policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

When you use co-branded services or those provided by a third party within CGI-Central, your Personal Information may be passed to that third party provider. Its use of your Personal Information is subject to their applicable privacy policies. 

### We are using Google Remarketing

We use Google Analytics’ 3rd-party audience data such as age, gender, and interests to better understanding the behavior of our customers and work with companies that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain ads on this website or other websites because we contract with Google and other similar companies to target our ads based on information we or they have collected, including information that was collected through automated means (such as cookies and web beacons). These companies also use automated technologies to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

You may opt out of the automated collection of information by third-party ad networks for the purpose of delivering advertisements tailored to your interests, edit or opt-out your Google Display Network ads’ preferences at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>.

### Information We Do Not Collect

When you visit our site, we do not collect your name, email address or any other Personal Information unless you provide it to us.

### Purchases

If you are make a purchase from CGI-Central, your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date are requested. This information allows your orders to be processed and fulfilled. Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose.

Wherever CGI-Central collects Personal Information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

### Security

Wherever your Personal Information may be held within CGI-Central or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.

CGI-Central may use a shopping cart feature that safeguards your Personal Information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) certificate. SSL software encodes data transferred between you and the server. CGI-Central is not responsible for any Personal Information you disclose to third party affiliates that do not use SSL software or do not offer a secure way to transfer information.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

### Third Parties

Some pages on the CGI-Central web site include links to third party web sites. These sites are governed by their own privacy statements, and CGI-Central is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Users submitting information to or through third party web sites should review the privacy statement of those sites before providing them with Personal Information.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose Personal Information online (e.g., through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere) that information can be collected and used by others.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

All information obtained from the customer will be used for the sole purpose of completing the transaction and that none of this information will be sold, rented, leased, or otherwise released to any third party for any reason.

### Your Consent to This Agreement

By using CGI-Central website, you consent to the collection and use of information by CGI-Central as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Please email any questions about Privacy Policy to: [support@cgi-central.net](mailto:support@cgi-central.net)
